brafton.com 2012-10-16

# Privacy Statement

  1. ### General:

We are strongly committed to protecting users’ privacy, and this sets out our policy on the use of personal data relating to Users which has been collected in relation to their access to and use of the Site.

  2. ### Information collected:

Brafton utilizes various Javascript-based tracking softwares (notably Google Analytics) to gauge demographics and other relevant data of our on-site web visitors. We do not install any type of software that tracks you or your browsing device “outside the walls” of Brafton.com. If you wish to opt-out of any type of visitor tracking, we recommend disabling Javascript in your browser options.

  3. ### Use of information:

In general, we will only use the information you provide to us for the purpose for which such information was provided. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings from us by following the instructions set forth in the opt-out section below. We reserve the right to access and to disclose personal information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate our systems properly or to protect either ourselves or our users.

  4. ### IP addresses:

We use IP addresses to collect statistical information about the areas of the system that users are visiting, and general “traffic” data. Such information does not relate to the use being made of the system by a particular user in relation to identifiable items being viewed. This information allows us to determine what is most beneficial for its users, and facilitates us in continually improving the overall site for our users.

  5. ### Cookies:

A “cookie” is a small amount of data that is sent to a user’s browser from a web server and stored on a user’s computer, used to store and track information about the user. Brafton utilizes basic cookies to enable caching of our content in your browser to help accelerate page loading performance. You can disable cookie storage via your browser’s content settings.

  6. ### Customer Data Confidentiality:

Confidential customer data is the property of the customer. Brafton, Inc. will not use personally-identifiable confidential data without prior customer consent. We may use collective identified customer data and statistics for internal analysis and external marketing purposes only.

Confidential login information may be provided to Brafton employees in the areas of technology and social media. Brafton employees are bound to strict privacy regulations and confidentiality agreements forbidding the sharing of any client login credentials. Only employees with direct interaction with that particular account shall have access to the information.

  7. ### User-submitted Materials:

Brafton, Inc. does not claim ownership of the materials you provide, upload, or submit through our website or our services. By posting, uploading, or submitting your information you are granting to us, our affiliated companies, and our sublicensees, permission to use your content in connection with the operation of our and their businesses. We are under no obligation to post or use any content you may provide and may remove any content at our sole discretion.

By providing your content you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your information as described in this section including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload or submit this information.

  8. ### Security:

The Site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet, we will take reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personal information.

  9. ### Updating information:

Should we use e-mail news alerts or other services to which you sign up, we will allow users the option to change or modify information previously provided. This may be done through the following methods:

    * e-mail the information to [updates@brafton.com](mailto:updates@brafton.com); or
    * visit brafton.com, and follow the on-screen instructions.
  10. ### Cancellation:

Should we use e-mail news alerts or other services to which you sign up, we will upon your request, we will deactivate your information from our active databases. To make this request, send an email to [deregister@brafton.com](mailto:deregister@brafton.com) . Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law. We will retain in our files some personal information you may have requested to remove, solely in order to keep an archival set of records and to comply with legal requirements as required or permitted by law. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. However, such personal information will only be available to select personnel at Brafton.com .

  11. ### Opt out:

Should we use e-mail news alerts or other services you sign up, you may opt-out of receiving communications from us, by the following means:

    * send an e-mail to [optout@brafton.com](mailto:optout@brafton.com); or
    * visit brafton.com, and follow the on-screen instructions.

Last revised 29th November 2011
